

# MILAP CHAVDA DIGITAL MARKETER

#### **CONTACT INFORMATION**

Mobile Number : 9662692932

Email ID : Milapchavda007@gmail.com

A2 Milind Park Flat, Nr Favourite Residency, Memnagar, Ahmedabad

#### PERSONAL PROFILE

i have overall 3+ years of experience in sales and marketing field. A highly organized and hard-working individual looking for a responsible position to gain practical experience. Secure a responsible career opportunity to fully utilize my training and skills, while making a significant contribution to the success of the company.

#### **INTERESTS AND HOBBIES**

- Spend a time on Discover new things in Digital marketing
- Stock trading
- Singing
- Watching Movies Explanation

#### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

#### DIGITAL MARKETING EXECUTIVE

OneClick IT Consultancy (March 2021 to Present)

- Plan and execute all Web, SEO On-Page, Off-Page, Social Media Marketing, Manage Website & Reporting.
- Improving the usability, design, content and conversion of the company website
- Devising strategies to drive online traffic to the company website
- Evaluating customer research, market conditions and competitor data.
- Measure and report performance of all digital marketing campaigns, and assess against goals (ROI and KPIs).
- Provide creative ideas for content marketing and update website

#### DIGITAL MARKETING EXECUTIVE

XIMPLE SOLUTIONS (Oct 2019 to March 2021)

- Build, plan and implement the overall digital marketing, including SEO, marketing database, email marketing, social media, content creation, WordPress design and updates.
- Performing ongoing keyword research including discovery, competition analysis and optimization of keyword opportunities
- Coordinating with U.S.A. Marketing, Sales and Content teams to optimize customer experience and ensure brand consistency
- Build strong customer relationships through social media interaction like LinkedIn
- Measure performance of digital marketing efforts using a variety of Web analytics tools (SEMrush, Google Analytics, Ahrefs etc.)
- Optimizing keywords and other SEO factors in web pages for search engine optimization
- Owned all email planning and execution of email marketing campaigns. Led customer segmentation efforts to trigger automated tagging and sending of emails based on user interactions with our customer platforms

#### **HOME LOAN COUNSELOR**

HDFC SALES PVT LTD. (Dec 2017 to May 2019)- 1.5 Years

- It is basically sales and marketing profile. Business Outsourcing from Builder, Broker, and others Financial Advisors. Coordinate to customer, builder, credit, legal, technical person from Login to Disbursement Process.
- Generating Lead From Open Market. Push For Maximum Sales
- Core product :All Kinds of Home Loans
- Supporting product : Insurance, Mutual funds, Education
- Achieving 3rd Rand In PAN INDIA Group 3 in Highest Login Files in 3 Months

# WHY I CHOOSE CAREER IN DIGITAL MARKETING?

There's no getting around the fact that almost all businesses, sooner or later, must include digital in their marketing activities. And with the demand for digital marketers outweighing the supply, there are plenty of opportunities out there for those looking to get into the field also i like this field.

### SKILLS & ABILITIES

- Motivated, well-disciplined individual
- Finds joy in assisting others
- Passionate About Work
- Result Oriented
- Digital Marketing
- Search Engine Optimization
- Social Media Marketing
- Pay Per Click
- Email Marketing
- Graphic Designing
- WordPress Website

#### COURSES

#### MASTER OF DIGITAL MARKETING

Brandveda institute of Digital Marketing May 2019 to Sep 2019

#### GRAPHIC DESIGNING

TOPS Technology May 2019 to Aug 2019

#### **EDUCATIONAL HISTORY**

## **MBA in Information Technology**

**ICFAI** University of Distance Learning

#### BBA

Som Lalit Institute of Management

Graduated in May 2017, Achieved 63 % & 1st Class

#### 12th

Saraswati Vidhyalay

HSC - May 2012 to April 2014 Achieved 73 % & 3rd Rank in School

#### **MY PERSONAL SITES**



🔀 • indianadscompany.com

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**



**Advanced Digital Markeeting** Brandveda



amazonin Amazon Trained Ecommerce Specialist



Google Digital Unlocked



**Become a Digital Marketing Specialist** LinkedIn Learning

# TOPS Graphic Designing Training Program TOPS Technologies



I Declare that I will prove myself as an icon if you given me the opportunity to serve in your esteemed organization.

Milap Chavada